<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Angels and Devils (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.AngelsAndDevils</packageId>
  <author>Sandy</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/AngelsAndDevils</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Sandys mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2048192285

[img]https://i.imgur.com/CN9Rs5X.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/AngelsAndDevils][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
This mod adds Angels and Devils as races into Rimworld. No special powers, just aesthetic.

***LORE***
      In another dimension, Light and Darkness existed in an age where nothing else yet existed. The Absolute Being split the light and created the Fragments of Light and issued the command to protect the world. As for the darkness, it was split into Pieces of Darkness and had received the command to destroy the world. Because of this, these two forces were always at war with each other.

     It was all an entertainment for The Absolute Being. As time passes, both Fragments of Light and Pieces of Darkness had slowly realized this and they yearned for freedom. The only way to be free was to escape to a different dimension where The Absolute Being's power would never enslave them. They escaped into our dimension and that costed them their bodies.

    To continue to live, they have had to possess soulless human bodies. Those humans that got resurrected retained their selves, but also inherited the inherent personalities of the souls. Those possessed by the Fragments of Light became really kind people and those possessed by the Pieces of Darkness, became psychopaths. Thanks to these magical beings, these humans were bestowed with a very long lifespan and were super-immune to diseases.

    Because of their personalities, the people of our world started calling these resurrected humans as Angels and Devils.
AND, thats how we got Angels and Devils in Rimworld.

***Special features per race***

Angels:
 - Always have Kind and Super-immune Traits.
 - Can tame and train animals, better than humans.
 - Can medical tend and operate, better than humans.
 - 50% less butchering speed and yield.
 - Wont participate in raids, but will defend themselves if needed.
 - Better social skill.

Devils:
 - Always have Psychopath and Super-immune Traits.
 - Can hunt stealthily, better than humans.
 - Can construct and mine, better than humans.
 - 50% more butcher speed and yield.
 - Will participate in raids.
 - Better resistance to toxic buildup and psychic drones.

Both races are mixed into the vanilla factions. But you wont find the angels in the Savage tribe and Pirate factions.

***Save game***
Its a race mod, so removing from any existing game/save, will break the game.

***Load Order***
Load this mod after Humanoid Alien Races mod. You can find that mod in this link, https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=839005762

***Disclaimer***
The wand and the trident, used in the preview image are not included in the mod.

***Author***
Myself (Sandy)

***Credits***
 - Tynan, for creating the game.
 - erdelf, for creating the Humanoid Alien Races Framework mod.
 - Kasmex Forever #0915 - preview's commissar, for the great preview image.
 - Control Assuming Director, in discord, for helping with Angel Wings texture.
 - Everyone in Rimworld discord who helped me with the mod.
 - Everyone in Humanoid Alien Races discord who helped me with the mod.
 - Lore was inspired by Solo Leveling manhwa.

***License***
MIT License; Copyright (c) 2020 Billy Barnes

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>